{
    "id": "a38d1f3df6bb48d6a90b7a94f2ffa488",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am going to …………………. with your brother when I am in town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get in touch",
                "have touch",
                "getting in touch"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9727f9d3d9cd4d1f878a6b61b8bff789"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I found her she was ……………… with cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blue",
                "red",
                "green"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c0e69f9e9cb46a69e74e0146dd59479"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is Mary …………………. the phone. She wants to talk to you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4e6aa9d5442c423eb0294e7ba360e17a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can’t implement your plans before ……………….. them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "discussing",
                "discussing about",
                "discussing after"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e82180d42644c31871ec18c8b4604e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which flight is she traveling …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5f2f005327a54ef888fab245eb5277bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… in this city for twenty years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am living",
                "have lived",
                "had lived"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4220fb9f962d4175b7eaf4ba9e0ba4a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… her since she was a child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bdfbf0a536854a3f9ca2b58649903f91"
        },
        {
            "question": "The kettle ………………… Shall I make tea?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "boils",
                "has boiled",
                "is boiling"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5a692a3a01854fd58f53cac48626b424"
        },
        {
            "question": "Heat ………………… bodies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expand",
                "is expanding",
                "expands"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1ba475fb94874caf9259b8ac2df2c795"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ………………… Spanish.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "spoke",
                "can speak"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d539a44e41684f3faf3639070f5098f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those plates belong ……………….. the top shelf.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "29e5f815bbc648ceaba86360effb00c8"
        }
    ]
}